Me and Kobayashi got into a fight.
Kobayashi, you're a dummy!
You butt-face!
I'm still scared to go back home,
but the sky is so dark and I'm getting sleepy.
I'm going to go find somewhere brighter.
So many humans, lots of big beltings.
What is this loud voice?
It looks fun.
My tummy's hungry.
Thanks for coming by.
That looks good.
Appreciate it.
595 yen.
Hey there, what do you want?
Oh, Japanese money.
Sorry, but I'm afraid you can't use that here.
I'm afraid we don't accept the end.
He talks funny.
Are you alone here?
Where's your mom?
Why are you always acting like that?
Let's go get some U.S. dollars from your mom.
I'm always serious.
The hot dogs won't go anywhere, so take your time.
I'll give you a good discount when you come back.
Let me tell you.
No, I totally get it.
What's the matter?
You okay?
Did you space out or something?
Yes.
Still yen.
You need to pay with our country's money if you want to buy stuff.
I can't use money here.
Not many humans on this street.
Somebody help me, please!
Get back here, you little brat!
Stop running right now!
No!
You'll never catch me!
What you doing?
I'm sorry I didn't see you there!
Why are you running?
Isn't it obvious?
They're being chased!
Those guys are bad!
I gotta go!
I get that.
I'll save you.
You'll save me!
But help!
Out of the way, kid!
Move!
What the heck?
Michael!
Who is that brat?
What the hell did she just do?
How dare you hurt Michael like that!
He's not feeling well!
He already had the runs today!
Oh!
Hey, wait!
Let's go.
You saved my life!
Thank you!
You're freakishly strong for someone your age, know that?
Wait a sec!
Are we in New York?
Hi!
My name's Chloe!
Kana.
Kana!
Chloe, why were they chasing you?
They kidnapped me!
And I just found out that they're in the Mafia.
So I'm trying to stay low-key.
Mafia?
Is it bad?
Yeah!
That's why I took off running when I thought the coast was clear!
Poor Chloe.
My dad is the CEO of an important company.
He publicly opposes the Mafia.
They're using me to get to him!
They're not here now!
Let's go play!
Huh?
You wanna go where?
What?
I'm bored.
Let's go play.
Huh?
Yeah, okay.
I can play with you.
Huh?
You're hungry.
I'll buy you some lunch as a thanks.
Yay!
Let's go, Chloe.
Huh?
Okay.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
This is perfect.
It can stay out longer.
Anything to keep from going home.
A black card?
I'm sorry, we don't take credit cards at the hot dog stand.
I usually don't carry much cash on me.
Anyway, this is my first time exploring New York City.
I usually just stay on our mansion grounds and don't go anywhere.
Does this mean you're rich, Chloe?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
So you scream a lot?
Like her?
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
What...
What's this happen?
Boy, she doesn't sound very happy.
She plays with me a lot, too.
There are all kinds of people, huh?
Yeah.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Let's get started.
I'm sorry.
I had a fight with Kobayashi and ran away from home.
But it was all because of something I did.
It's my fault.
I should head back now.
Are you sure?
Are you sure it's safe?
What if?
What if they're still mad when you get back?
What if they won't forgive you after you apologize?
Doesn't that scare you?
Yes, it does.
But I'm more scared of not having a home and nowhere to go.
Chloe?
Come on.
Let's go home.
Listen.
Kana, I...
I can't just...
Chloe!
Geez, I never knew kidnapping a crafty runaway would be such a boring and easy job.
I think a little punishment should liven things up.
Shut it and give me the tape.
Right here, Michael.
Hey, just make sure you don't damage the goods.
One tiny arm ain't gonna make much of a difference.
I was wrong. I never should have run away.
I would do anything to be back home.
I'm so sorry, Papa!
What the? What?
It's so dark.
Go check the breaker, you dope.
Breaker?
I'll go do it. Stay here.
Ow! That hurts.
Lock your step!
Sorry about that.
Oh, my God.
Don't eat me! I taste gross!
Chloe.
Huh? I know that voice.
Let's go home.
Wait.
Kana?
Amazing!
Am I dreaming right now?
Or maybe those jerks actually killed me?
Are we flying around heaven, Kana?
It's not a dream.
Can you tell me where you live?
I'm in Minnesota, so probably there.
It's just past those big lakes.
I see them.
You're so soft and so warm.
I lied to you.
I ran away.
They didn't kidnap me.
You too?
Yeah.
I had a fight with my papa.
I need to apologize.
But I don't know what to say.
Me neither.
But if someone's still there after things get bad.
Even when you get mad at them.
And say mean things like you hate them.
If there's somebody who stays, I'm sure it'll be okay.
Yeah.
Are you ready to go home too, Kana?
Will I see you again?
If you want, I'll give you my address.
You have an address?
Oh, hi.
And where have you been all this time?
Lady Toru.
I'm so sorry.
Well, I'm not the one you should be apologizing to.
I know you're right.
Where's Kobayashi?
Have you decided what you're going to say when she wakes up?
No idea.
Unless Kobayashi said the same thing.
I was watching you the whole time.
Oh.
Okay, I'm heading out.
Be safe out there.
See you later, Miss Kobayashi.
I'm off to work now.
Okay, take care.
It's so hot.
Oh, hey, Kana.
You're awake.
Good morning.
Morning.
Kobayashi, are you off work today?
Yes, good night.
Oh.
I was super busy until yesterday.
Death March style?
Super Death March style.
Next up, we have Kobayashi.
Kobayashi.
Hello, friends.
Kobayashi here.
Today we're trying to...
Where are Lady Toru and Yolobu?
They're both working until this evening for a change.
Are you just going to laze around the house all day long?
Mm-hmm.
I'm going to be super lazy.
Might be a good day for you to go play with Saekoa.
I can't.
Saekoa said she's going on a family vacation today.
Looks like a boring day for you, then.
Bean jam, huh?
That looks tasty.
Mm-hmm.
Kobayashi, can I have a watermelon?
Huh?
I didn't hear them mention watermelon.
No, Lady Toru bought one yesterday.
Wow, you're very observant.
Okay, we'll have it this afternoon.
It's hot.
So hot.
What are you doing?
Kobayashi.
There.
Are you ready for lunch?
Yeah.
Okay, I'll get it started.
Do you think you could go downstairs and check the mailbox for me, pretty please?
Can we have some mini-tomatoes?
Ta-da!
Easy to make!
Wow.
Air mail, huh?
I wonder if it's from that new friend you said you made in New York the other day.
Oh, Chloe.
She says she wants to come over and play with me.
Is it okay if she stays for a bit?
Sure, of course.
Really?
Oh, boy!
I can't wait to meet her.
So sweet!
Kobayashi, we don't have any more tea.
Huh?
Out already?
If I don't make any, we only have milk.
Oh, well.
Let's go buy some.
We're going out?
Looks like it.
Hana, where's your hat?
I got it.
Let's go, please.
I'm here.
Hat?
Where are we going?
I don't know yet.
Let's explore.
Oh.
Wonder, wonder, wonder, wandering.
Maybe you'll find some things for your picture diary.
I can look for stuff for my research, too.
I hope you find something amazing.
Hmm?
Lady Toru said I should research foods from the other world that you might like her to cook sometime.
Maybe as a surprise.
I see.
Why don't we do something else now?
Ants.
Hmm?
Lots of ants.
Oh, you're right.
I wonder if they have a little home under that manhole.
Manhole?
But for ants?
Hmm.
It's actually made for a human.
There's a path for sewage beneath the ground here that runs all over the city.
Does that mean there are more lids on the ground?
Mm-hmm.
Yep.
Way too many, in fact.
Oh.
Okay.
I'll hunt them.
Huh?
I found another one.
Hey, very good.
This another research project?
Over there.
You'll find a lot of them on this street.
This one's the same.
This one's square.
That's for a fire hydrant.
This one's similar but kind of different.
Right.
Kinda...
Kobayashi!
I found another one.
Great.
Kobayashi, are you okay?
Oh, sure.
That was a great exercise for an indoor person.
Oh.
This is so cool.
Ow.
I guess dragons can get a brain freeze, too.
Yours looks very yummy.
Do you want to try some?
Yeah.
Kobayashi, look.
Hmm?
Oh.
Oh, wow.
You found a colorful one.
Looks interesting.
Has it always been like that?
It's weird that I've lived here so long and never noticed it.
Is it some kind of character?
It's Mr. Quiet.
So you recognize him.
He's the talk of the town.
That's enough.
Oh, great.
Random monsoon?
Let's go, Kana.
Retreating.
Are you hanging in there, Kana?
Yeah.
I protected my notebook.
Good for you.
Well, we may as well just go swimming now.
What was that?
That's pretty cool.
Well, what do you expect?
Just a typical summer downpour.
Typical downpour?
Rainy, rainy, rain, rain.
Downpour.
It's a rainy monsoon.
Stop summoning it.
Howl away.
Thunder so strong.
Sing a song of rain.
This is not good.
Watch out for the equipment.
It's Mr. Quiet.
The head is too big.
That's what the manhole picture was of?
Put your head.
Yes.
Poor ladybug.
Oh, yeah.
It must have got washed away.
Is she dead?
It's alive.
Oh, yay.
It flew away.
I'm sure that it's going back home.
Oh, she has a home?
Everyone does.
Oh.
Rainbow.
It sure looks like one.
Mm-hmm.
And now the rain's completely stopped.
Toru and the others should be getting home soon, too.
You ready, Kana?
Come on.
It's time to go home.
Home.
Next time I want to bring a camera.
You should.
We're home.
Welcome back.
You're so late.
Let's eat.
I'm hungry, too.
Where were you two all day today?
Hmm.
Here and there.
It was so fun.
Right?
Something fun without me?
No fair!
Can we please eat?
Eat!
That's wicked.
Huh? What is?
Sorry, I'm still getting used to not being in the Big Apple.
Kana, you're too easily influenced.
Don't wait up. I'm going to a party with a friend.
You're going to Psychoist to play, right?
This week on Who's Rotten?
Virgo.